let us see if we understand how caches
can become incoherent suppose that we
have a memory location a that initially
contains a zero value in this system we
have three cores each core has its own
right back
l1 cache and these right back caches do
not have any coherent support this means
that these right back l1 cache is simply
behaved as if each of these caches was
just alone in a uniprocessor so they
behaved correctly for a uniprocessor
cache but they do not try to maintain
coherence and this is what the three
cores do called zero loads from a into a
register increments the value in the
register and then stores the register
back into memory location a some time
later
core one does pretty much the same thing
it loads a into a register increments
and writes the register back to a and
finally core 2 does the same thing note
that these are happening one after the
other
so without caches core zero would be
loading zero writing a one read one
encore one put a two back in a and then
here we read two and put a three but
with the three l1 caches and no coherent
support the question for you is the
value that core a is writing to a here
can be what can it be zero can it be one
can it be - can it be three can it be
for and can it be something larger than
four put a check next to all of the
answers that might be true for this
right here